[
    {
        "question" : "Meaning of 'Chicken Feed' ",
        "optionA" : "A very small money",
        "optionB" : "A huge money",
        "optionC" : "Food for thought",
        "optionD" : "None of these",
        "answer" : "A very small money"
    },
    {
        "question" : "Meaning of 'Cost an Arm and a Leg' ",
        "optionA" : "War hero",
        "optionB" : "Very expensive",
        "optionC" : "Scene in battle field",
        "optionD" : "Very cheap",
        "answer" : "Very expensive"
    },
    {
        "question" : "Meaning of 'Fly by night'",
        "optionA" : "Night journey",
        "optionB" : "A Bird busy in night",
        "optionC" : "Cat's eye",
        "optionD" : "Swindler",
        "answer" : "Swindler"
    },
    {
        "question" : "Synonym of Exhort",
        "optionA" : "Weak Plea",
        "optionB" : "To urge strongly",
        "optionC" : "Beg",
        "optionD" : "Borrow",
        "answer" : "To urge strongly"
    },
    {
        "question" : "Antonym of Blunt",
        "optionA" : "Easy",
        "optionB" : "Lazy",
        "optionC" : "Sharp",
        "optionD" : "Speedy",
        "answer" : "Sharp"
    },
    {
        "question" : "Antonym of Brave",
        "optionA" : "Achieve",
        "optionB" : "Gain",
        "optionC" : "Give",
        "optionD" : "Cowardly",
        "answer" : "Cowardly"
    },
    {
        "question" : "Synonym of Abjure",
        "optionA" : "To give",
        "optionB" : "To take back",
        "optionC" : "Happy",
        "optionD" : "Sorry",
        "answer" : "To take back"
    },
    {
        "question" : "Synonym of Abrogate",
        "optionA" : "Create",
        "optionB" : "Run",
        "optionC" : "Fascinate",
        "optionD" : "Abolish",
        "answer" : "Abolish"
    },
    {
        "question" : "Unfortunately, he_______ a lot of money to the bank",
        "optionA" : "Borrowed",
        "optionB" : "Owed",
        "optionC" : "Deposited",
        "optionD" : "Lent",
        "answer" : "Owed"
    },
    {
        "question" : "I ______ the apartment all day yesterday.",
        "optionA" : "Clear",
        "optionB" : "Washed out",
        "optionC" : "Cleaned Up",
        "optionD" : "None of these",
        "answer" : "Cleaned Up"
    },
    {
        "question" : "Choose the word spelt correctly.",
        "optionA" : "Maxculine",
        "optionB" : "Massculine",
        "optionC" : "Masculine",
        "optionD" : "Macsculine",
        "answer" : "Masculine"
    },
    {
        "question" : "Choose the word spelt correctly",
        "optionA" : "Begining",
        "optionB" : "Beginning",
        "optionC" : "Beignning",
        "optionD" : "Begininng",
        "answer" : "Beginning"
    },
    {
        "question" : "Choose the word spelt correctly",
        "optionA" : "Ambulance",
        "optionB" : "Ambulence",
        "optionC" : "Ambulancs",
        "optionD" : "Ambalence",
        "answer" : "Ambulance"
    },
    {
        "question" : "Choose the word spelt correctly",
        "optionA" : "Criticice",
        "optionB" : "Criticael",
        "optionC" : "Criticise",
        "optionD" : "Criticese",
        "answer" : "Criticise"
    },
    {
        "question" : "hoose the word spelt correctly.",
        "optionA" : "Substandial",
        "optionB" : "Substantial",
        "optionC" : "Substential",
        "optionD" : "Substendial",
        "answer" : "Substantial"
    },
    {
        "question" : "Synonym of Botch",
        "optionA" : "Positive Effort",
        "optionB" : "Blessing",
        "optionC" : "Mild",
        "optionD" : "Clumsy Effort",
        "answer" : "Clumsy Effort"
    },
    {
        "question" : "Synonym of Brusque.",
        "optionA" : "Polite",
        "optionB" : "Curt",
        "optionC" : "Speed",
        "optionD" : "Enjoyu",
        "answer" : "Curt"
    },
    {
        "question" : "Synonym of Chagrin.",
        "optionA" : "Delight",
        "optionB" : "Levy",
        "optionC" : "Vexation",
        "optionD" : "Give up",
        "answer" : "Vexation"
    },
    {
        "question" : "Synonym of Congruent",
        "optionA" : "Of different shape",
        "optionB" : "Of the same shape",
        "optionC" : "Salute",
        "optionD" : "Dispose",
        "answer" : "Of the same shape"
    },
    {
        "question" : "Synonym of Copious",
        "optionA" : "Less",
        "optionB" : "Good",
        "optionC" : "Discourage",
        "optionD" : "Plenty",
        "answer" : "Plenty"
    }
]


 
